Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - LOC 50.4d, 1975, c75/032 (Box-folder 17/33)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Lyle Scholz. Includes song categories. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Kalam.
  - LOC 50.4e, 1976, c76/034 (Box-folder 17/34)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Lyle Scholz. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Kalam.
  - LOC 50.4f, 1982, c82/035 (Box-folder 17/35)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth with Lyle Scholz. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Kalam.
  - LOC 50.4g, 1982, c82/036 (Box-folder 17/36)
  - LOC 50.4bb, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 17/37)
    Huang, Jean and Donna Milton "Emic Statement." Includes song categories, titled transcriptions, interval succession charts and emic transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Kalam.
  - LOC 50.4bbb (folder 1 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box-folder 17/38)
    Interval Succession Charts by Vida Chenoweth. Student Works Related to the Kalam Music System. Includes emic statement, song categories, song text translations and song structure analysis. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Kalam.
  - LOC 50.4bbb (folder 2 of 2) (Box-folder 17/39)
    Chenoweth, Vida "Kalam Songs." Report includes general characteristics, pitches and purpose of the Kalam music system.
  - LOC 50.5a, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 18/1)
    Sound Recording Log. Correspondence. Collected by Ken Tropu. Correspondence from Vida Chenoweth to Mrs. Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province.
  - LOC 50.5b, 1982, r78/027 (Box-folder 18/2)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Ken Tropu. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province.
  - LOC 50.6, c80/028 (Box-folder 18/3)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province.
  - LOC 51a, r68/04 (Box-folder 18/4)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons Province.
  - LOC 51b, 1974, c74/181 (Box-folder 18/5)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Charles Duvel. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons Province.
  - LOC 52, 1981 (Box-folder 18/6)
    Niles, Don "Kamu Mariria: Music of the Maopa and Aloma" Boroko, Papua New Guinea. Song Categories and song text translations of sound recordings collected by Les McLaren and Ilaita Gigimat. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, Maopa/Aloma.
  - LOC 52.1 (folder 1 of 3), 1983 (Box-folder 18/7)
    Excerpts from the Diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.1 (folder 2 of 3), 1984 (Box-folder 18/8)
    Webb, Michael "Sogeri Singsing." Boroko, Papua New Guinea. Booklet containing song text analysis and song categories of various music systems of Papua New Guinea. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.1 (folder 3 of 3), 1983 (Box-folder 18/9)
    Event Program. "Sogeri Traditional Dancing. Konedobu Cultural Centre. Friday June 3, 1983." Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.2, 1983 (Box-folder 18/10)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Karen Hudson. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.3, 1983 (Box-folder 18/11)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.4, 1983 (Box-folder 18/12)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.5, 1983, c83/191b, c83/192 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - LOC 52.5a, 1983, c83/192 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - LOC 52.6, 1993, c93/795 (Box-folder 18/15)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Evan Pillsbury. Papua New Guinea, Central Province, various languages.
  - LOC 52.7, 1988 (Box-folder 18/16)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Ukarumpa, Usarufa.
  - LOC 53 (Box-folder 18/17)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Sheridan and Smart. Papua New Guinea.
  - LOC 54, 1959 1958, r59/153 (Box-folder 18/18)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Ray Brown. Papua New Guinea, Southern Highlands District/Province, Duna.
  - LOC 54a (folder 1 of 2), 1967, r67/154 (Box-folder 18/19)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dennis and Nancy Cochrane. Includes song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, Southern Highlands District/Province, Duna.
  - LOC 54a (folder 2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 18/20)
    Chenoweth, Vida "An Investigation of the Singsing Styles of the Dunas." Brisbane, Australia. Correspondence. Interval Succession Charts. Transcriptions. Report includes interval analysis, song structure and song text analysis. Correspondence from Vida Chenoweth to the editor of Oceania and from "Nan" and Dennis" to Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Southern Highlands District/Province, Duna.
  - LOC 54.1, 1967 (Box-folder 18/21)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dr. Harland Kerr and Marie Kerr. Papua New Guinea, Southern Highlands District/Province, Witu/Wiru.
  - LOC 54.1aa, 1968 (Box-folder 18/22)
    Chenoweth, Vida "A Preliminary Investigation of Witu Songs." Brisbane, Australia. Includes interval inventory, song structure analysis, phrase syntax, interval succession charts and transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, Southern Highlands District/Province, Witu.
  - LOC 54.2, 1970 (Box-folder 18/23)
    Franklin, Karl " Metaphorical Songs in Kewa." Sydney, Australia, 1970. Song text translations and analysis. Directory of Pacific linguists. Papua New Guinea, Southern Highlands District/Province, Kewa.
  - LOC 55 (folder 1 of 2), 1983 (Box-folder 18/24)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse and Claire Bureau. Sound recording is a compilation of commercial releases. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, various languages.
  - LOC 55 (folder 2 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 18/25)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Buka Island, Uisai.
  - LOC 55a, 1983 (Box-folder 18/26)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse and Claire Bureau. Sound recording is a compilation of commercial releases. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons Province, various languages.
  - LOC 55b, 1983 (Box-folder 18/27)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Kieta.
  - LOC 55c, 1984 (Box-folder 18/28)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Notes on Aerophones and the Sing-Sing at Hanahan, Buka Island. Papua New Guinea, Buka Island.
  - LOC 55.1, 1983 (Box-folder 18/29)
  - LOC 55.1a, 1983, c83/319 (Box-folder 18/30)
  - LOC 55.2, 1983, c83/320 (Box-folder 18/31)
  - LOC 55.2a, 1983, c83/320 (Box-folder 18/32)
  - LOC 55.3, 1976-1983, c83/321 (Box-folder 18/33)
  - LOC 55.4, 1969-1983, c83/322 (Box-folder 18/34)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse and Claire Bureau. Sound recording is a compilation of commercial releases. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons Province, Tinputz/Teop.
  - LOC 55.5, 1982, c82/182 (Box-folder 18/35)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Mortlock Islands.
  - LOC 55.6 (folder 1 of 2), 1983, c83/200 (Box-folder 18/36)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Karen Hudson and Ruth Colgren. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6 (folder 2 of 2), 1983 (Box-folder 18/37)
    Interval Succession Charts by Vida Chenoweth. Titled transcriptions by Roxan F. Kelly. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6a, 1984 (Box-folder 18/38)
    Sound Recording Log. Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Sound recording collected by Harold Wilkin and Jennifer Runner. Includes song categories. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6b, 1984, c84/404 (Box-folder 18/39)
    Sound Recording Log. Includes song text analysis. Collected by Harold Wilkins. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi/Rotokas.
  - LOC 55.6c, 1984, c84/401 (Box-folder 18/40)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harold Wilkin. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6d, 1984, c84/402 (Box-folder 18/41)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Tim Cooley. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6e, 1984, c84/403 (Box-folder 18/42)
  - LOC 55.6f, 1984, c84/400 (Box-folder 18/43)
  - LOC 55.6g, 1984, c84/405 (Box-folder 18/44)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harold Wilkin and Jennifer Runner. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6h, 1984, c84/406 (Box-folder 18/45)
  - LOC 55.6i, 1984, c84/407 (Box-folder 18/46)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harold Wilkin. Includes song titles and song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6j, 1984, c84/468 (Box-folder 18/47)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.6k (folder 1 of 2), 1984, c84/468 (Box-folder 18/48)
  - LOC 55.6k (folder 2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 18/49)
    Wilkin, Harold "An Investigation into the Emic Intervals of the Kunua Music System." Wheaton, Illinois. September 10, 1984. Saperstein, Kathy "Retest of Kunua-Hahone Analysis Check." Wheaton, Illinois. June, 1986. Worksheets by Harold Wilkin. Worksheets include transcriptions and interval succession charts. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Kunua.
  - LOC 55.6aa, 1985 (Box-folder 18/50)
    Wilkin, Harold "A Preliminary Analysis of Nasioi Music." Wheaton Illinois. January 31, 1985. Wilkin, Harold "An Analysis of Nasioi Music." Wheaton, Illinois. March 1, 1985. Reports include emic interval analysis, transcriptions, interval succession charts, titled transcriptions and interval flow charts. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nasioi.
  - LOC 55.7, 1983 (Box-folder 19/1)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Moses Havini. Includes Song categories and song text transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Haku/Hako.
  - LOC 55.7a, 1984, c84/463 (Box-folder 19/2)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Tim Cooley. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Hako.
  - LOC 55.8 (folder 1 of 2), 1984, c84/420 (Box-folder 19/3)
    Sound Recording Log. Map. Collected by Jennifer Runner. Song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Teop/Tinputz.
  - LOC 55.8 (folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box-folder 19/4)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Transcriptions of Scriptural Songs. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, various languages.
  - LOC 55.8a, 1984 (Box-folder 19/5)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jennifer Runner. Song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Teop/Tinputz.
  - LOC 55.8b, 1984, c84/422 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - LOC 55.8c, 1984, c84/423 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - LOC 55.8d, 1983, c83/229 (Box-folder 19/8)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Teop/Tinputz.
  - LOC 55.8e, 1983, c83/230 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - LOC 55.8f, 1983, c83/231 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - LOC 55.8g, 1984 (Box-folder 19/11)
    Runner, Jennifer "A Checking Session at Teop Island." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes interval succession charts and emic transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Teop/Tinputz. January 28, 1984.
  - LOC 55.8aa (Box-folder 19/12)
    Introduction to the song styles of Teop Island, North Solomons Province of Papua New Guinea. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Teop/Tinputz.
  - LOC 55.8aaa (Box-folder 19/13)
    Article on Teop Island written for The Encyclopedia of World Music. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Teop/Tinputz.
  - LOC 55.9 (folder 1 of 5), 1984 (Box-folder 19/14)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harold Wilkin. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia.
  - LOC 55.9 (folder 2 of 5), 1984 (Box-folder 19/15)
    Includes interval inventory and etic interval analysis. Cooley, Timothy J. "Analysis of Ethnic Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia/Solos/Haku/Hako. February 27, 1984.
  - LOC 55.9 (folder 3 of 5), 1984 (Box-folder 19/16)
    Cooley, Timothy J. Analysis of Ethnic Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes interval inventory and etic interval analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Haku/Hako. July 20, 1984.
  - LOC 55.9 (folder 4 of 5), 1984 (Box-folder 19/17)
    Cooley, Timothy J. "Analysis of Ethnic Musics." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes interval inventory and etic interval analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Haku/Hako. August 24, 1984.
  - LOC 55.9 (folder 5 of 5), 1983 (Box-folder 19/18)
    Titled Transcriptions. By Timothy Cooley. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia/Haku/Hako.
  - LOC 55.9a, 1984 (Box-folder 19/19)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Timothy Cooley. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia.
  - LOC 55.9b, 1984 (Box-folder 19/20)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Timothy Cooley. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Solos.
  - LOC 55.9c, 1984, c84/464 (Box-folder 19/21)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harold Wilkin and Timothy Cooley. Includes song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Haku/Hako.
  - LOC 55.9d, 1985, c85/499 (Box-folder 19/22)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Susan Richardson and Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia.
  - LOC 55.9e, 1985, c85/498 (Box-folder 19/23)
  - LOC 55.9f, 1994 (Box-folder 19/24)
    Report. By Vida Chenoweth. Includes ethnographic information, microtonal analysis, Transcriptions and interval flow diagram. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia.
  - LOC 55.9aa (folder 1 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 19/25)
    Saperstein, Kathy "Retest of Halia Analysis Check." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes contrasting etic units and interval inventories. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia/Solos. June, 1986.
  - LOC 55.9aa (folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box-folder 19/26)
    Cooley, Timothy J. "Analysis of Ethnic Musics." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes interval inventory, etic comparisons and titled transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia/Solos. February 27, 1984.
  - LOC 55.9d,ee 1985 (Box-folder 19/27)
    Richardson, Susan and Christine Patterson "Preliminary Analysis of Halia Songs." Richardson, Susan "Results of Analysis Check of Halia Music." Wheaton, Illinois October 12, 1985. Includes microtone hypotheses, analysis of emic intervals and titled transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia. February 27, 1985.
  - LOC 55.9ee (folder 1 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 19/28)
    Richardson, Susan " An Analysis of Halia Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Graduate Thesis. Chapter titles: Preliminary Analysis, Results of Analysis Checking Session and Melodic Grammar and Syntax. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia.
  - LOC 55.9ee (folder 2 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 20/1)
    Richardson, Susan " An Analysis of Halia Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Graduate Thesis. Chapter titles: Preliminary Analysis, Results of Analysis Checking Session and Melodic Grammar and Syntax. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Halia. 12/16/1986.
  - LOC 55.10, 1984 (Box-folder 20/2)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jeff Meyer. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Nagovisi. 6/9/1984.
  - LOC 55.11, 1984 (Box-folder 20/3)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. Jul 7, 1984-Jul 8, 1984.
  - LOC 55.11a, 1984 (Box-folder 20/4)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Margie Griffin. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. Jul 9, 1984.
  - LOC 55.11b, 1984 (Box-folder 20/5)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Margie Griffin. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 7/11/1984.
  - LOC 55.11c, 1984, c84/410 (Box-folder 20/6)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jennifer Runner. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 7/25/1984.
  - LOC 55.11d, 1984 (Box-folder 20/7)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jennifer Runner. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 7/27/1984.
  - LOC 55.11e, 1984 (Box-folder 20/8)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jeff Meyer and Margie Griffin. Includes song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 10-Jul-1984-11-Jul-1984.
  - LOC 55.11f, 1964-1969, c64/444 (Box-folder 20/9)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Margie Griffin. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin.
  - LOC 55.11g, 1964-1969, c68/445 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - LOC 55.11h, 1964-1969, c69/446 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - LOC 55.11i, 1964-1969, c64/447 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - LOC 55.11j, 1964-1969, c68/448 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - LOC 55.11k, 1983 (Box-folder 20/14)
    Sound Recording Log. Original control number: c83/224. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin.
  - LOC 55.11l, 1983 (Box-folder 20/15)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin.
  - LOC 55.11m, 1983, c83/225 (Box-folder 20/16)
  - LOC 55.11n, 1983, c83/226 (Box-folder 20/17)
  - LOC 55.11o, 1983, c83/227 (Box-folder 20/18)
  - LOC 55.11aaa (folder 1 of 3), 1985, c83/228 (Box-folder 20/19)
    Sound Recording Log. Document recital by Jeff Meyer. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 2/15/1985.
  - LOC 55.11aaa (folder 2 of 3), 1984 (Box-folder 20/20)
    Meyer, Jeffrey "Preliminary Analysis Music of the Buin Language Group." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes interval inventory, etic comparisons and titled transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 2/27/1984.
  - LOC 55.11aaa (folder 3 of 3), 1985 (Box-folder 20/21)
    Meyer, Jeffrey "Senior Document in Ethnomusicology: An Analysis of Buin Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes preliminary analysis of emic intervals, results of analysis, grammatical analysis, titled transcriptions and song categories. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. Feb-1985.
  - LOC 55.11bb, 1984 (Box-folder 20/22)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 07-Jul-1984 - 8-Jul-1984
  - LOC 55.12, 1984 (Box-folder 20/23)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jack Pankinu. Includes song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Uisai. 23-Jun-1984 - 25-Jun-1984
  - LOC 55.12a, 1984, c84/419 (Box-folder 20/24)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jeff Meyer and Jack Pankinu. Includes song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Uisai. 21-Jun-1984, 31-Jun-1984.
  - LOC 55.12aaa (folder 1 of 3), 1984 (Box-folder 20/25)
    Meyer, Jeffrey " Results of Analysis Checking Session based on Preliminary Analysis of Music in the Buin Language Group." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes summary of emic intervals and etic interval comparison. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Buin. 7/9/1984.
  - LOC 55.12aaa (folder 2 of 3), 1986 (Box-folder 20/26)
    Check of Preliminary Intervals of Usai Music. Preliminary analysis by Duane Clouse. Checker Paul G. Grose. Original Document "An Emic Analysis of Usai Music" included. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Uisai.
  - LOC 55.12aaa (folder 3 of 3) (Box-folder 20/27)
    Clouse, Duane "Music data of the Uisai language group." Includes titled transcriptions, emic interval comparisons, interval succession charts and interval inventory charts. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Uisai.
  - LOC 55.13, 1984 (Box-folder 20/28)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harold Wilkin and Timothy Cooley. Includes song text analysis. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Rotokas. 6/28/1984.
  - LOC 55.13a, 1985, c85/487 (Box-folder 20/29)
    Sound Recording Log. Recording of a seminar given by Vida Chenoweth and an unnamed parliamentarian. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Rotokas. Jun-1985.
  - LOC 55.13b, 1986, c86/551 (Box-folder 20/30)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Paul Grose. Compositions for a music literacy class hosted by Vida Chenoweth and students. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Rotokas. 7/8/1986.
  - LOC 55.13aa (folder 1 of 2), 1983 (Box-folder 20/31)
    Filkin, Kaye "A Preliminary Investigation of the Emic Intervals of the Rotokas Music System." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes emic interval comparisons, song categories and titled transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Rotokas. 2/28/1983.
  - LOC 55.13aa (folder 2 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 20/32)
    Partial Transcription by Vida Chenoweth. Grose Paul G. "An Emic Analysis of Rotokas Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes interval inventory, etic comparisons, interval succession charts and titled transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, North Solomons, Rotokas. 2/16/1986.
  - LOC 56, 1996 (Box-folder 20/33)
    Chenoweth diary and Tanna Music Analysis. Papua New Guinea, Vanuatu, Tanna Island. 05-1996.
  - LOC 56a, 1996 (Box-folder 20/34)
    Chenoweth diary and Tanna Music Analysis. Papua New Guinea, Vanuatu, Mota Island.
  - LOC 60, 1982-1998 (Box-folder 20/35)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, Gulf Province, Akoye. Sept-1982 - 26-Apr-1998.
  - LOC 80 (folder 1 of 2), 1963, r62/282 (Box-folder 20/36)
    Sound Recording Log. Correspondence. Collected by Vida Chenoweth and Eunice Pike. Includes ethnographic report. Mexico, Oaxaca, Mazatec.
  - LOC 80 (folder 2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 20/37)
    Chenoweth, Vida "A Partial Analysis of the Musical Style of the Wantoat Tribe of New Guinea." Analysis. Papua New Guinea, Wantoat.
  - LOC 80.1, 1987 (Box-folder 20/38)
    Sound Recording Log. United States.
  - LOC 80.2, 1957-1958, c89/706 (Box-folder 20/39)
    Sound Recording Log. Mexico, Chiapas, Spanish/Tzotzil. Dec-1957 - Mar-1958.
  - LOC 80.3, 1965, c65/532, c65/532a (Box-folder 20/40)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Joy McCarthy. Mexico, Yucatan. Aug-1965.
  - LOC 80.4a, 1965, r65/279 (Box-folder 20/41)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dean Arnold. Mexico, Yucatan.
  - LOC 80.4b, 1965, r65/280 (Box-folder 20/42)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dean Arnold. Mexico, Yucatan, Spanish. Aug-1965.
  - LOC 80.4c, 1965, r65/281 (Box-folder 20/43)
  - LOC 80.5, 1962, r62/282 (Box-folder 21/1)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Mexico, Oaxaca, Mazatec.
  - LOC 81, 1987, c87/593 (Box-folder 21/2)
    Sound Recording Log. Sound recording is a commercial release. Guatemala.
  - LOC 81.1, 1960, r60/278 (Box-folder 21/3)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Guatemala, San Jorge, Atitlan.
  - LOC 81.2, 1968, c91/726 (Box-folder 21/4)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Bob and Mary Gunn. Panama, Buglere, Wounaan/Waunun.
  - LOC 81.2a, 1968, c91/727 (Box-folder 21/5)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Ron and Kathy Binder. Panama, Wounaan/Waunun.
  - LOC 82a, 1982, c90/707 (Box-folder 21/6)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dean Arnold. Sound recording is a commercial release. Ecuador, Quichua/Quechua Spanish.
  - LOC 82b, 1982, c90/708 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - LOC 82c, 1982, c90/709 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - LOC 82.1, 1979, c79/261 (Box-folder 21/9)
    Sound Recording Log. Ecuador, Jivaro/Shaar.
  - LOC 83a, 1986, c86/521 (Box-folder 21/10)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Carole Swain and Milton Camargo. Brazil, Roraima, Ninam. Mar-1986.
  - LOC 83b, 1986, c86/522 (Box-folder 21/11)
  - LOC 83c, 1986, c86/523 (Box-folder 21/12)
  - LOC 83.1, 1963, c63/531a (Box-folder 21/13)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Joy McCarthy. South America, Brazil. Jul-1963 - Aug-1963.
  - LOC 83.2, 1988, c90/722 (Box-folder 21/14)
    Sound Recording Log. Sound Recording Log. Brazil, Surui.
  - LOC 84 (folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box-folder 21/15)
    Excerpt from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Peru, Pajonal Campa. 18-Jul-1985 to 26-Jul-1985.
  - LOC 84 (folder 2 of 2), 1985 (Box-folder 21/16)
    Shaler, Dorothy " Analysis of the Music System of the Pajonal Campas of Peru." Wheaton, Illinois. Graduate Thesis. Chapter titles: Preliminary Analysis, Field Analysis Check and Grammar and Syntax. Peru, Pajonal Campa. Dec-1985.
  - LOC 84a, 1970 (Box-folder 21/17)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. Peru, Pajonal Campa. Feb-1970.
  - LOC 84b, 1974, c74/442 (Box-folder 21/18)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. Peru, Pajonal Campa. Jun-1974.
  - LOC 84c, 1974, c74/443 (Box-folder 21/19)
  - LOC 84d, 1975, c75/457 (Box-folder 21/20)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jackie Willis. Includes names of performers. Peru, Pajonal Campa. 3/10/1975.
  - LOC 84e, 1975, c75/458 (Box-folder 21/21)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jackie Willis. Includes names of performers. Peru, Pajonal Campa.
  - LOC 84f, 1975, c75/459 (Box-folder 21/22)
  - LOC 84g, 1974, c86/533 (Box-folder 21/23)